Office of the Registrar. Administrative files of Stanley Chin, William Puckett. 1919-1987. UARC.0561
UCLA Library Special Collections
Office of the Registrar. Administrative files of Stanley Chin, William Puckett.
1919-1987
UCLA Library Special Collections
UARC.0561
5.4 Linear Feet (1 box, 5 cartons)
Record Series 561 contains the administrative files of registrars Stanley Chin and William Puckett, generated within the Office of the Registrar at the University of California, Los Angeles. The files of Chin and Puckett include some materials generated by registrars Pomeroy and Showman.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9934669923606533
Historical note
The following people have served as Registrar (or Recorder) at the University of California, Los Angeles:
Harry M. Showman - 1930-1942
William C. Pomeroy - 1942-1957
William Puckett - 1957-1972 (Registrar Emeritus, 1972-1993)
Stanley Chin - 1972-1982
Scope and Content
Record Series 561 contains the administrative files of registrars Stanley Chin and William Puckett, generated within the Office of the Registrar at the University of California, Los Angeles. The files of Chin and Puckett include some materials generated by registrars Pomeroy and Showman. Files include correspondence, statistics, reports, memos, meeting minutes, proposals, and forms regarding enrollment, registration, and grade distribution of students at the University of California and the University of California, Los Angeles. Additionally, administrative files regard budgeting, policies, and operations of the Registrar.
This is an inactive record series; no additional University records are expected to be added.
- Grades., 1957-1973. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Legal actions., 1963-1971. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Special scholarships, etc., actions., 1970 Spring. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Advanced standing., 1966. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Mulit-term courses., 1966-1967. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Pass-Fail., 1966-1969. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Fire - buildings., 1968-1970. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Scope and Content
  Regarding fire prevention and safety.
- Registrar - Records Management Committee., 1964-1966. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Honors., 1957-1966. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Status lapse., 1951-1975. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- College of Letters and Science., 1940-1972. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- School of Dentistry sample student records., 1969. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- MD (medical student) Seniors., 1971-1973. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Directives and procedures for Student Health., 1963-1981. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Deceased student., 1968. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Criticisms., 1964-1972. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Defense Language Institute (Army Language Institute) at Monterey., 1962-1964. (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Continuous registration., 1965-1982. (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 1969 Summer Quarter., 1968-1969. (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Foreign students., 1963-1970. (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Agencies requesting reports on students., 1963-1972. (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Transcripts., 1959-1965. (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Summer Quarter visitors., 1967-1968. (Box 1, Folder 23)
- North American Aviation, Inc. Educational Reimbursement Program., 1963. (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Units at graduation., 1968-1969. (Box 1, Folder 25)
- School of Law., 1949-1951. (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Law School - certificates., 1963. (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Data Processing Center (DPC) charges., 1969-1970. (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Budget information - campus or statewide., 1957-1970. (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Fiscal Facts., c.1966. (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Comparative Scholarship., 1966-1969. (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Scholarship actions., 1952-1970. (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Other scholastic reports from offices., 1951-1970. (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Withdrawal figures., 1951-1972. (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Scholarship grade distribution reports., 1951, 1963-1970. (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Grade distribution semester reports., 1955-1961. (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Annual grade distribution reports., 1956-1966. (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Athletes - scholarship., 1956-1969. (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Academic probation, dismissal - Coordinate Council., 1965-1968. (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Chancellor., 1950-1966. (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Space utilization - schedule of classes analysis., 1952-1969. (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Class-size frequency., 1956-1957. (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Committee on Courses of Instruction - approval of graduate courses., 1963-1972. (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Space, staff, students., 1950-1951. (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Emergency plan., 1970. (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Graduation matters., 1965-1968. (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Instructional load and cost., 1933. (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Management Information System Committee - Academic Services., 1970. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Office., 1931-1952. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Notes - Winter registration instructions., 1969-1970. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Field House enrollment - On-Line Enrollment (OLE) System problems., 1967. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Student Evaluation of On-Line Enrollment (technical report)., 1970. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- On-Line Enrollment Evaluation., 1971. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Proposal for On-Line Enrollment System at UCLA., 1967. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Enrollment., 1970. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Online - letters., 1963-1977. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Official study list and reference study lists., 1966. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Enrollment system - policy and cost., 1968-1975. (Box 2, Folder 11)
- OLE SYS (Online Enrollment System)., 1970-1975. (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Release of information - Online Enrollment System., 1968-1971. (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Correspondence with DPC - release of records., 1967-1972. (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Automated Pre-Enrollment Proposal., c.1970. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- General administrative file., 1987 Spring. (Box 2, Folder 16)
- General administrative file., 1987 Winter. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Fee deferral letters., 1986-1987. (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Publicity., 1987 Winter. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- General administrative file., 1986 Fall. (Box 2, Folder 20)
- General administrative file., 1986 Spring. (Box 2, Folder 21)
- General administrative file., 1986 Winter. (Box 2, Folder 22)
- General administrative file., 1985 Fall. (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Freshman Summer Program (FSP) students., 1985. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- General administrative file., 1985 Summer. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- General administrative file., 1985 Spring. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- General administrative file., 1985 Winter. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- General administrative file., 1984 Fall. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Olympics., 1984. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Posters., 1974-1984. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Registrar., 1932-1947. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Reports of the President [of the University of California]., 1958-1965. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Building Committee - Administration Addition., 1952-1968. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Subject A on Record Card., 1967. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Reports on Registrar., 1930, 1957-1966. (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Handbook., 1958-1974. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Student handbooks., c.1970-1975. (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Student handbooks and illustrated map of UCLA campus., 1971-1974. (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Publications Committee., 1960-1971. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- UCLA forms., 1941-1961. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Materials [from] other institutions., 1945-1961. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- University of Michigan registrar procedures., 1947. (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Campus Computing Network - charges., 1969-1970. (Box 3, Folder 20)
- On Line accounts., 1970-1971. (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Campus Computing Network., 1972-1973. (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Campus Computing Network., 1971-1972. (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Registration/enrollment., 1972 Fall. (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Online enrollment., 1972 Spring. (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Registration and enrollment., 1971 Fall. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Registration and enrollment., 1971 Winter. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Registration and enrollment., 1971 Spring. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Enrollment., 1970 Fall. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Summer sessions., 1970. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Enrollment., 1970 Spring. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- University of california Summary Report of Operations., 1956-1959. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Campus protest questionnaire., 1969. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Correspondence., 1971 August-1972 December. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Correspondence., 1974-1981. (Box 4, Folder 10-16)
- [Office of the] President [of the University of California]., 1936-1942. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Regents., 1946-1955. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Dean of Students., 1945-1972. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Minutes - Deans., 1947-1950. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- President [of the University of California]., 1948-1962. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Memos - Admissions System., 1945-1972. (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Grading and other policies., 1950-1972. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Evaluation - Normal School credits., 1955-1956. (Box 5, Folder 8)
- College of Applied Arts., 1946-1971. (Box 5, Folder 9)
- American History and Institution requirement., 1958-1974. (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 99 course/Angela Davis., 1969. (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Supplement to statistical addenda., 1946. (Box 5, Folder 12)
- 1881-1956 enrollment figures. (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Statistics., 1955-1961. (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Summer Sessions, Berkeley., 1952-1960. (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Summaries of students., 1948-1961. (Box 5, Folder 16-18)
- Register book., 1919-1931. (Box 6, Folder 1)